
Sprecher 1  (00:00)
Or your voice? 

Sprecher 2  (00:03)
From being deeper, we all little bit on one chest, had a cold or so. 

Sprecher 1  (00:09)
Patel. Are you called cortices of India? 

Sprecher 2  (00:16)
Years like Earth. 

Sprecher 1  (00:18)
Oh, my God. 

Sprecher 2  (00:20)
Best greetings from home. 

Sprecher 1  (00:25)
That's why with people 

Sprecher 2  (00:28)
Hey, a little bit well, I think it's just a mirror of a few days. So how are you doing your mother on side? 

Sprecher 1  (00:43)
Yeah, the birth and you are here at the gentle with machine. Hmm, that Mr moon and Jain. 

Sprecher 2  (00:52)
Rakhein, I love everybody in Nice to hear you. 

Sprecher 1  (00:56)
Wow, hello. 

Sprecher 2  (01:02)
So what are yesterday? I sent updated schedule of the next deliveries? I sent them to Yu chain ancient, hope you get this. 

Sprecher 2  (01:16)
I think I forgot the controversy cabinets. They are scheduled to have a luck La la La. La. 

Sprecher 2  (01:33)
Get no confirmation until now, but I think they will be on side on the 90s too and waiting for the confirmation. They will get a flat within this week. 

Sprecher 1  (01:47)
You might think 19, is this 

Sprecher 2  (01:50)
Yes, I think so. I send a confirmation as soon as I gathered. 

Sprecher 1  (02:11)
Is the eighth unit? The quantity of the segment is the h? 

Sprecher 2  (02:19)
Massava areas. 

Sprecher 1  (02:22)
OK. 

Sprecher 2  (02:23)
I send you the list of of cabinets when I get the confirmation. So, but as I wrote in my email transport capacities and I think they have been down to mall as 0, but they are shrinking more and more, and this, I've been told yesterday and doing some interviews, I had with transport companies. They are telling me this will be uh, a rising issue until the end of January. 

Sprecher 2  (03:02)
So this is already the time when our last Our transports have to be on side, so Good timing. So better we are just working on this end, as you see, sometimes we get um, 1 or 2 flights together, sometimes we have to be a little bit patient. I've seen some reports related to the work hour, electrical engineers and the 2 new ones we have are doing. 

Sprecher 2  (03:43)
Answer, please let me remind everybody. And if we have been in the start moving any of our drives, don't care if it's the orchestra pit the winches on the site, tell us, please be aware that these parts are well cleaned before and please be aware that safety is informed before If you are moving the orchestra, we get, I don't know how many of these guys who the red west, a running around on side, just having an eye on if the forklift is growing backward, they check, if there is nobody there give our orchestrates are moving. 

Sprecher 2  (04:31)
We have to have one down there in the orchestrated, to have a look if nobody there is working there or so. If you're moving windships, the sly bar windshes, you are also moving fly bars, and if they are going down too fast, and there's anybody standing um, beside them, you know, you can hurt somebody, so please be aware that nobody is moving nothing without safety on side, OK. 

Sprecher 1  (05:04)
But like other fish, yes, you know, there is yesterday, we all share with all the colleagues I know the operator also, they knows, are you already not here arm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm. 

Sprecher 2  (05:18)
Okay, by the chin, this is here and my daily responsibility to care for this and I'm not on side, so it's just us and I think more Mr moonshi or my office on side everybody shall assist you with this. We have really, really have to take care of this. But okay, if especially these electrical guys, are informed, and they have to wait until everything is cleared and safety is it is in short 

Sprecher 1  (06:02)
In the room. OK, next It bought them is your eating right on knowing, um. The yesterday, I caught up with the killer. 

Sprecher 2  (06:18)
Which one Catholic or Superman? 

Sprecher 1  (06:23)
None face nothing else. 

Sprecher 2  (06:27)
Okay. 

Sprecher 1  (06:29)
It's a becomes the way which means you urgency. Our current, it's a manufacturing airline. Unfortunately, you know that which they are the idea. 

Sprecher 2  (06:48)
I have the On the support of the track engineering department, he's broken. I think so I tried to reach fiscal. Um, the supplier, who is working on these drawings and promised to deliver them 2 weeks ago I tried to reach them yesterday without success I will try to reach them today again. 

Sprecher 2  (07:17)
I escalated his intention to didn't robbery niche boss off the track. Subside or you just to try if he can can reach anything, because fiscal is his supplier and hope to get these wrongs today. But I absolutely don't know what is open there on or not. 

Sprecher 2  (07:43)
Why they didn't deliver it before because they promised to send it 2 weeks ago. Just hoping to get anybody English-speaking of this check company on the phone. And to get an information, there I know how urgent isn't just a blame for us that we didn't deliver it weeks before. 

Sprecher 1  (08:06)
So um, we have like the plan of plumbi if we develop is the India this year in between drawing, we have to buy You'll woman by anyone. It will come turn babu. 

Sprecher 3  (08:48)
Musasam Kuman mujh ji yahan Singh Yeh h* kuch hai. 

Sprecher 1  (08:54)
With the fourth one, why not yeah, but do you know you? What, if you really, you know the 2? So what we Uh, have to do in this moment because Now we exactly are kings with a keeper zcumbers. 

Sprecher 1  (09:19)
Yeah, it cannot help you exactly what kind of doing. 

Sprecher 2  (09:34)
Just don't understand your question, I know what we can do or what we have to do I know what we are missing and I know that these drawings, our arrest, an announce to be delivered by his confiscal, is you know, they are delivering paths and doing some construction work for the chuck colleagues. And also, these seat banking systems is completely and renewed by fiscal. Iss, so I hope by now, what we are missing already and what is open there and is not I can try it, try to communicate and to arrange the next steps, but I've been talking to Pita Catholic related to this topic um, in the last 2 weeks, more months, and he's been in contact with them, and so they should know what is all So I hope I get a reply today and get one of them on the phone and then we are having in new status. 

Sprecher 2  (10:47)
I know it's not only the the motor right for the bicone, it's also drawing for for the pins and for the Angus of the sequence system, and as we've been talking to end of next week, Thailand Mr shin at me, just that wants to try them to do their own drawing on construction and own system. Does anybody know if this is ongoing? 

Sprecher 1  (11:20)
Yeah, my heart is a similar period sharing 

Sprecher 2  (11:26)
Yes, I have seen it. 

Sprecher 1  (11:28)
A good pride is in balcony, as we had invention. 

Sprecher 3  (11:39)
Ab tumne Nanga, he na chuka h*. 

Sprecher 1  (11:46)
How much common info 

Sprecher 3  (11:49)
Okay, with a ray Richard of the ji show ki show Prem Toh Maine palace thae. B****, also, which is our relevant, you can actually them after my own political change, something which general talk with more omitra. We have shared both the scores on prashanskaran. 

Sprecher 1  (12:09)
So I will see that is flat size here. And it was an eloquency claim, or we don't have a teeth knowing Or main aapki, her Hindi cheese or Peeter Kumara with the NIT rained to wine Yeh. Thoda. 

Sprecher 1  (12:41)
Write on Munna. Can you return now? 

Sprecher 2  (12:48)
Yes, but this is main hall, right? 

Sprecher 1  (12:52)
Yeah, yeah, this is made of yes, like A But now, the week of war is coming 

Sprecher 4  (13:05)
I'm a complete 

Sprecher 1  (13:06)
Like you will 0. 

Sprecher 2  (13:08)
Hello, Mr. Wang, nice. Yeah, you 

Sprecher 4  (13:14)
So now we know the ka very Lakshmi, vaidukri, each of gangulya Virendra, Bhumika, she looks a picholatha. 

Sprecher 1  (13:27)
From Chrome. Uh. When you return the but then although there was a changing, so it's driving him greatly. 

Sprecher 4  (13:43)
Okay, no I did you know how the Puja the church Nadi Khanna Pani Puri, vitamin of khatani chin khaas yahan Toh chadhya? 

Sprecher 1  (13:52)
And promising he wants already here, so most of them will kept job and planning your earlier, but Most of them is changing employ. 

Sprecher 4  (14:07)
Agram Dhara Churu, she to major yeah, they were afloan rickobe, American hotel of the achieve April. Would you like which I took last long chhichhore taram? 

Sprecher 1  (14:18)
The hope of these sharing It's a week without the reveal to my job. Time cannot do anything so dear with bye, it's a big Davis or the other manufacturing? 

Sprecher 1  (14:44)
No, Toh seeton, mechanic hai, our is the design king or a herogy, so both of them is involved another project each 

Sprecher 4  (14:58)
You know the process of Ah, you building on the court. 

Sprecher 1  (15:03)
This is not a digit method because after finishing of this project, ma'am, okay, they can changing other project good. Now we have so many, many server can be issue in this moment. So the just have a horror the no is kind of fact Hoon, aa, chemism, big problems 

Sprecher 4  (15:32)
No, you know, the woman become umr ashrama, does 

Sprecher 1  (15:35)
Owe or yeah, were prepared in the official either. 

Sprecher 4  (15:39)
Ullu, from Vidyarthi, very cool and Thach of the companies, they should also ka poochha milao Rahul, he logic project, a proportional, it was very low polite star. 

Sprecher 1  (15:52)
Oh, they were Ram, meethi official vendor our board member ek, Dundee, kalaon, per you know. 

Sprecher 4  (16:06)
Looks a lot. There is a king of me. Some rural things have 2 mother of agenda, you know, the Shankar Avenue, Chakraborty, muthaon, legiora. 

Sprecher 1  (16:14)
There is no heaven Roman. Have you ever span to the July 12? 

Sprecher 2  (16:21)
Yes, I watch. 

Sprecher 4  (16:23)
Because I should not become equal what the cabinet alone space of higher classical adaja thapur to their namoji, heavy Yantur, hijammu, chanandu, Rachel shanqui. 

Sprecher 1  (16:36)
Go which we did today, okay. They are waiting for the information about all our electric cabinet number. It is not compound here. 

Sprecher 4  (16:46)
Amit Yogi sa Bodh khushhasa, vijayada, Roy Hyderabad answering people touched the visitor of puchal, madam Mundra, research in the Hindus, amusing. Moti, the job, how did they call Krit khatm? Gujarat? 

Sprecher 4  (17:00)
It is, how about there 

Sprecher 1  (17:03)
Irrespective and also, so several, which will remain the upcoming the item so time across the culture, a compensation. Yes. I don't go wonder if this is the right thing. 

Sprecher 4  (17:20)
Kupu psycho he swachhi, muthandaman, like we have. The battery is much more than one. 

Sprecher 1  (17:25)
And the flap up the yeah, weekend prime wicket is 70 problem now which you want better candan is taught. So there is the empty 

Sprecher 4  (17:38)
Okay, the achichamphony ek chamate Hain ise Yeh, chuke. He consequence of a tourist from UK is all we have growth nicha Vidya kumhan, rotten, guru Mana Yogi is not available? 

Sprecher 1  (17:54)
Not so another tradition is a cotton cleaner or 2 weeks ago. There was a problem at the because there is that enough money for the cotton, you know, thank though it's why journey set a pretend for this subcontinent pressure this week, a tough, find your problem happened again, because though we have A Appliances 2 item for the constant cleaner era is or locations system. Another one was a heavy assistant, but it turns check the field was the item which don't have enough money for the income player. 

Sprecher 1  (18:43)
The teminray is waiting writing at the With the airport 

Sprecher 2  (18:50)
Yeah, I sent a bile related to this yesterday. I am yes either, but I 

Sprecher 4  (18:57)
The third number 1 AM to continue to ayurvedan. Strongly. We get this to walk him in east kaha, Chief Minister Chanchala Hiram, now, it was a holiday, yeah, we have the everybody Hota ye naraajneeti, ke swachchhe uthana, yuva secondly, in your face communication is running, our English generate, each one is very female genie. 

Sprecher 4  (19:17)
He is aranjasoos, no cabinet, Shram, kasam or Gandhi. Bhanyaan. 

Sprecher 1  (19:25)
And you prepare the cabinet delivery step. What we deliver if there is something 1 about 2 is their absent is acting that the order wiring works. 

Sprecher 4  (19:42)
Atri, Andra, maybe the switch other. Why don't you should give it? 

Sprecher 1  (19:46)
How could is go to the capital? 

Sprecher 4  (19:50)
The nature of impchava yashumda ye Khan, dekhima swachchha, mutabing, Hain irctub initiative. 

Sprecher 1  (19:59)
Or rejoiced, the MP has decreen ab Abhinay is very hardly Stone. 

Sprecher 4  (20:07)
Weak, every challenge. It has been ashagan, I was a home neither is a Mishra, okay, he ko consocation of khedana Dharam. 

Sprecher 1  (20:19)
So we must check EA happiness of 57 

Sprecher 4  (20:25)
You should rugging up. 

Sprecher 1  (20:27)
We work to check that 

Sprecher 2  (20:30)
Aam, nutritional this, that's We've got some empty cabinets are all s not empty, but on a mechanical complete, but they are not cabied on wired. But what is the problem? Now that's what I didn't understand. 

Sprecher 2  (20:54)
We can do the selection of the main consumption which get all our species and fuses installed as far as I know, if there are some no no on the first and there should be nothing missing so we can install and attach the man consumption. 

Sprecher 1  (21:18)
Try out these issues after the stocking. So the moon and we were explaining 

Sprecher 2  (21:26)
Or indeed, okay, fine. Okay, bad sure. Sure, I am alowa and joala that these incomplete cabinets are big issue and will be in the next weeks, 2I am surely aware of this too. 

Sprecher 4  (21:44)
Can you reach home? Would you live by uchan kevri Nande Mein vehicle with a Uchcha Leo anjuvo she would approve east the options of Ajab Puri from purval nagi, technology, oxygen modified. 

Sprecher 1  (22:00)
The tame of the room. 

Sprecher 1  (22:21)
It's a video I wish, yeah, every progress we are being going on. The Muslim Buddha is a vital here, most of them is 

Sprecher 2  (22:34)
No problem, but I am here in Germany checking all our most important issues now is to get this delivery issues solved. And this is what I'm looking on. Second is to push our suppliers if there's anything left open, if that quality issues and we say, I am not getbored yeah, it's enough to do me on this side too. 

Sprecher 2  (23:01)
And I think this week's maybe I am more helpful here on side because I'm going around through A Logistic Partners to our supplying Partners and so on, and maybe it's not a waste of time that I'm here now I hope so And I am really on duty in coming from morning to evening like you are used to 

Sprecher 1  (23:25)
Yeah, I'm so sorry to win here the your voice. How are you? H support right? 

Sprecher 1  (23:34)
Her voice sound different. 

Sprecher 4  (23:42)
Arab hotel come to khangra, something called the number of Wala. 

Sprecher 1  (23:46)
Yet, for a God, why not? Yes? 

Sprecher 4  (23:51)
The yogistry statement Ruchi khoma is over pradhamad could either ek movie the case of Rajat, ma'am home. 

Sprecher 1  (23:58)
When you staying here, you just short, shut that wrongly. Well, it's when you return in Germany why you corrector 

Sprecher 2  (24:11)
This happens sometimes. Yeah, come down just a matter off. I wish you were having long days and this is what I had in Korea too. 

Sprecher 2  (24:24)
And so I think it's not a middle of the place where I am. 

Sprecher 4  (24:31)
She means what you could say, one of them, and there you could sit as a Lakshya Mukhya kuttiha shukriya, ko eushreyan to each haji ko hai in his own Hardik jab pahunchi with time, you know, giridambra. 

Sprecher 1  (24:44)
So when you stay here, we talk about the ego there another chain. You know, when you attend Germany, you must have top with the connects and 

Sprecher 2  (24:59)
Good, yes, and I called a visit equation Khan. Just to be all tied and check what is going on there on how to help and how to speed up that production and the delivery schedule. 

Sprecher 1  (25:14)
OK, place this channel. 

Sprecher 2  (25:16)
Yes. Yes, I am absolutely doing I'm going to at. I'm going to us. 

Sprecher 2  (25:22)
I'm gonna check if forget all our spapart and our missing parts of our cabinets, what we can do to get this realise Fasta, what we can do to get our uh, missing path from the check suppliers to this is what I am doing. I'm doing this days just to have a little bit rough voice. Doesn't mean that I can move on and work Oh, should be sure. 

Sprecher 2  (25:47)
I am on duty the holiday. 

Sprecher 4  (25:51)
Hello, hello, again, the told. Those general will come your cooker motive, you component that rules about a similar high jaymor India, you know, which will change any matter of bunish real Absolute another issue. 

Sprecher 1  (26:10)
Pop-up your life in power. Yes, how about the this? 

Sprecher 2  (26:16)
Um nashka sham hua here, if you choose horror expensive transport, scheduled right now if that the acoustic panels and the um, the avertheal panels ready for shipment, I kept yesterday after cat 2 of us. The flow. Um, rather about 70% of this content just avoiding the last offer for the rest of it, and he's been quite expensive, but illness with the possibility and let me think they could deliver it until 28th of this month. 

Sprecher 1  (27:10)
Even why don't go Afternoon, shishpulan vivekanam Rama, ji Pawan, teen 0. 

Sprecher 4  (27:21)
From heaven Shivam, leja, Uncle to guwahan ke in England. 2 Uri, go achieve cabinet, se happiness or Pune, tejik, vyakt, yajari Mansha, vishing, Vishu ka bhi Mancha, Raha, tha chunko yogic, then as we don't get all the older compulsion. The engineering the pattern there is all which Hyderabad humility is 

Sprecher 4  (28:06)
journanda, there is huge and the brookandha. 

Sprecher 1  (28:12)
Why not we don't know for the electric cabinet? Now, it is not completely capital right from each okay. Baat hai operating is, in fact every night, why do we not ever plan to invite the age of level like me engineer? 

Sprecher 1  (28:34)
Yes, as we walked for 19 every time quiz, he explained to these the plan when they are coming here. How to what kind of problem 

Sprecher 2  (28:50)
Yeah, I can explain and now all these days, I've got 5 electrical experts for doing these internal cable works and one of them also able to to advise additional plasma that from the start on a beginning on on the second week of January, we will have 5 guys on side to start reworking all these. Cabinets. Just collecting all these missing parts and all table handas has been prepared. 

Sprecher 2  (29:34)
Until now, I'm gonna going to check with at during this week. If a war is complete, how they packed, how they prepared for the delivery, all these missing paths that have to be reward, starting beginning of January will be picked in On Friday this Friday and we've got a confirmed deliver a flat conference for mid of next week. So these parts will be on side in time. 

Sprecher 2  (30:18)
The rain rich, which Indian, just before the end of the month. So 

Sprecher 1  (30:27)
Okay, no more agree itananjigam takadme, another wo come hai, ko, hoga cabinet, hum man Ram, do that utaram there will be the member and for island we know who have gone hum Shram, do kaun jaye, Toh open ganjiraan Mein ko. Chhatra, Roha Toh OK, then you know you chat number, what's the head one? Hum bataukha, bhi dekha Hoon, Ajay. 

Sprecher 1  (31:00)
The paper for 10 years to tell me one whom Chicago in kids remember. 

Sprecher 2  (31:06)
Okay, okay, we have a plan what to do with each single cabinet. And we agreed to fix the sequence of finalising these cabinets on-site, because I will be there on the 10th of 10 year or 2, and so we will start altogether with reworking these cabinets as soon as then not let me start on this day and then we have to see how the local Surrounding is the able, which we should start first and in which sequence we cannot work. 

Sprecher 1  (31:48)
OK, Pita ko chahiye Toh yeshubhai musanjay or Kohli tab hai achhi anjaane Toh pahunche, nau nau, okay. 

Sprecher 4  (31:57)
Continue to kumapur in indepalpa, devacha mujhse Mann dein good in Amazon. Did you know 

Sprecher 1  (32:13)
I pull your feet right here. 

Sprecher 2  (32:16)
Organise my computer. 

Sprecher 1  (32:18)
15, about many times 

Sprecher 4  (32:24)
Take into the theorem. 

Sprecher 1  (32:25)
Okay, whatever happened, take on our Is this camera so sometimes it's right there. Make the thumb problem and So when hit their your original general 

Sprecher 4  (32:43)
These are also locational we are the true. What a little more. How much happened Yeh, hotel ka Chinta vikchetavati 

Sprecher 1  (32:56)
A 0 laugh alone, take here ompan, you Korea, we don't have any addition. A poem is change woman our gather. He had lost, checked 1 day every day, even every hour. 

Sprecher 2  (33:13)
I know I know working on weekends workout on playing a night. There has no buffer left. 

Sprecher 1  (33:22)
Please changing anymore. Or just deliver skin 

Sprecher 2  (33:28)
You you know that you know how I am working, you know that I am hardly working on this and just trying to to keep not only the scheduled transport but also may be transport earlier then I promised, but you know, I just can't do this, and this is all that's possible. And if it's possible, maybe I think I arranged it in the past, and hopefully you will do this in the future too. 

Sprecher 1  (34:00)
Again. 

Sprecher 4  (34:09)
Virakshika Mushroom, to wake up with edition. 

Sprecher 4  (34:29)
In the order that we wish we could finish high small holder. Yon yoshigi La dhilo ko Devon, dinon Shivika. 

Sprecher 4  (34:58)
What's up? Only you definitely like for their own eurial, total Toh ladsen or Mora, by reading 

Sprecher 1  (35:14)
Honour to a thinking of each other. 

Sprecher 4  (35:23)
Ki opportunity teacher for a mukhopal, who is a very genius newspaper radish for failure uttarakriti chahiye. 

Sprecher 1  (35:30)
Lots of sonic like cannot Keeping this. 

Sprecher 4  (35:36)
Making a college of the beaches in the origin, one of the 

Sprecher 1  (35:39)
Or your even you touch upon, you are 

Sprecher 4  (35:44)
So as there was a local course because of the 

Sprecher 1  (35:49)
Sorry for you are Get the form, hello, hello. 

Sprecher 2  (36:00)
Yeah, thank you about 

Sprecher 1  (36:01)
Either we ever heard some issue, though. Is there on your trigger? Why not you understand it very sort of drawing 

Sprecher 2  (36:20)
Yes, yes, yes, I really. And I am on it. It's just now, an hour, I tried to clock here and I'm trying to reach fiscal again. 

Sprecher 1  (36:31)
You know, and not the all the official letter deliver is we need to 

Sprecher 2  (36:37)
Yeah, OK, thank you. Now I am having called um, to catch the end and had interested for 3 part of an hour, so their absolutely, where what's happening here, too, and I'm just telling them again, what will happen. And I'm just 

Sprecher 1  (36:55)
Oh right now, they'just the one thing old age of the issue. Already, why did talk with Mrs. R and shanthaftam? 

Sprecher 1  (37:03)
So, but we cannot truly disappoint, because I don't the invoice amount so that's why they across Germany lenses of this 

Sprecher 2  (37:16)
Yeah, you send a mail related to this essent. I am in contact with army and he's gonna check what how to proceed and if you need any deviation allowance from kathyamala, she's the one who can do this, but I have in my call in half an hour. 

Sprecher 1  (37:38)
Yes, so today we have to contact with the armian weather. And we must receiving 100 million for your war each of reading today. Yes, otherwise so our resulting, we cannot be finishing the our energ. 

Sprecher 2  (37:54)
This is what you sent in the mail to and I will call 

Sprecher 1  (38:00)
The second born, is there please feedback to the intersalier? Yes, shris, are Singh solve this quantity? 

Sprecher 2  (38:10)
Yeah, I am on it are doing this yeah. 

Sprecher 1  (38:15)
Categore. 

Sprecher 2  (38:16)
Like guys, thank you here soon. I am I'm sending any invitation for a short call today again. Just to update between you and me, okay. 

Sprecher 2  (38:27)
Years old bye, guys, thanks for drowning. 

Sprecher 2  (38:43)
We have to highlight issues in here. 
